Guide to the Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
- Series XXXII. 1952
  - Chenango County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Clinton County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Columbia County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Cortland County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Delaware County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Dutchess County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Erie County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Essex County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Franklin County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Fulton County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Genesee County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Greene County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Herkimer County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Jefferson County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Lewis County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Livingston County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Madison County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Monroe County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Montogmery County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Nassau County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Niagara County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Oneida County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Onondaga County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Ontario County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Orange County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Orleans County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Oswego County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Otsego County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Putnam County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Rensselaer County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Rockland County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Saratoga County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Schenectady County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Schoharie County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Schuyler County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Seneca County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Steuben County, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Suffolk County, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Sullivan County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Tioga County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Tompkins County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Ulster County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Warren County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Washington County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Wayne County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Westchester County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Wyoming County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Yates County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Series XXXIII. 1953
  - Albany County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Allegany County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Broome County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Cayuga County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Chautuagua County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Chemung County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Chenango County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Clinton County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Columbia County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Cortland County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Delaware County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Dutchess County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Erie County I, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Erie County II, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Essex County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Franklin County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Fulton County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Genesee County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Greene County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Herkimer County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Jefferson County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Lewis County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Livingston County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Madison County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Monroe County, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Montgomery County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Nassau County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Niagara County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Oneida County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Onondaga County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Ontario County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Orange County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Orleans County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Oswego County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Otsego County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Putnam County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Rockland County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Schenectady County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Schoharie County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Schuyler County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Seneca County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Steuben County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Suffolk County, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Sullivan County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Tioga County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Ulster County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Warren County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Washington County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Wayne County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Westchester County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Wyoming County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Yates County, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Series XXXIV. 1954
  - Albany County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Allegany County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Broome County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Cayuga County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Chautauqua County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Chemung County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Chenango County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Clinton County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Columbia County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Cortland County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Delaware County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Dutchess County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Erie County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Essex County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Franklin County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Fulton County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Genesee County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Greene County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Herkimer County, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Jefferson County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Lewis County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Livingston County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Madison County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Monroe County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Montgomery County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Nassau County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Niagara County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Oneida County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Onondaga County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Ontario County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Orange County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Orleans County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Oswego County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Otsego County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Putnam County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Rensselaer County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Rockland County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Saratoga County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Schenectady County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Schoharie County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Schuyler County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Seneca County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Steuben County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Suffolk County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Sullivan County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Tioga County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Tompkins County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Ulster County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Warren County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Washington County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Wayne County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Wayne County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Westchester County, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Wyoming County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Yates County, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Series XXXV. 1955
  - Albany County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Allegany County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Broome County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Cayuga County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Chautauqua County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Chemung County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Chenango County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Clinton County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 81)
  - Columbia County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 82)
  - Cortland County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 80)
  - Cortland County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Delaware County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Dutchess County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Erie County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Essex County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Fulton County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Genesee County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Greene County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Herkimer County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Jefferson County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Lewis County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Livingston County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Madison County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Monroe County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Montgomery County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Nassau County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Niagara County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Oneida County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Onondaga County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Ontario County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Orange County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Orleans County, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Oswego County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 74)
  - Otsego County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 75)
  - Putnum County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 76)
  - Rensselaer County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 77)
  - Rockland County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 78)
  - Saratatoga County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - Schenectady County, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Schoharie County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 70)
  - Schuyler County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 71)
  - Seneca County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 72)
  - Steuben County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 73)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 79)
  - Suffolk County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - Sullivan County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - Tioga County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Tompkins County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - Ulster County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - Various Counties I, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Various Counties II, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Warren County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - Washington County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - Wayne County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - Westchester County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - Wyoming County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - Yates County, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 66)
- Series XXXVI. Farm and Home Bureau and 4-H Club Association
  - Albany Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Allegany Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Broome Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Cayuga Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Chautauqua Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Chemung Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Chenango Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Clinton Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Cortland Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Delaware Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Dutchess Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Erie Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Franklin Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Fulton Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Genesee Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Greene Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Herkimer Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Lewis Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Livingston Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Madison Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Monroe Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Montgomery Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Nassau Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Niagara Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Oneida Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Onondaga Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Ontario Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Orange Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Orleans Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Oswego Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Otsego Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Putnam Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Rensselaer Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Rockland Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Saratoga Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Schenectady Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Schoharie Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Schuyler Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Seneca Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Steuben Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - St. Lawrence Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Suffolk Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Sullivan Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Tioga Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Tompkins Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - Ulster Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - Warren Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Washington Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Wayne Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - Westchester Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - Wyoming Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Yates Farm, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 57)
- Series XXXVII. 1956
  - Albany County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 49-4)
  - Allegany County, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 49-3)
  - Broome County, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 49-2)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 49-1)
  - Cayuga County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Chautauqua County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Chemung County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Chenango County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Clinton County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Columbia County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Cortland County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Delaware County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dutchess County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Erie County I, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Erie County II, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Essex County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Franklin County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Fulton County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Genesee County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Greene County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Herkimer County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Jefferson County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Lewis County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Livingston County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Madison County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 17A)
  - Monroe County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Montgomery County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Nassau County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Niagara County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Oneida County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Onondaga County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Ontario County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Orange County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Orleans County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Oswego County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Otsego County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Putnam County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Rensselaer County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Rockland County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Schoharie County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Seneca County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Schuyler County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Steuben County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Suffolk County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Sullivan County, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 83)
  - Sullivan County, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Tompkins County, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 84)
  - Ulster County, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 85)
  - Warren County, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 86)
  - Washington County, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 87)
  - Wayne County, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 88)
  - Westchester County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Wyoming County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Yates County, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Series XXXVIII. Miscellaneous
  - Projects, 1917-1919 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - History of the Miami Flood Control Project, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - States Relations Service-Goddard S.H., 1918-1919 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Federal Appointments, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Plant Industry, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Readings in Rural Sociology, 1920 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - A decade of Utility Regulation in NYS, 1939-1940 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Memoranda-Soil Conservation Districts, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - "Study of Landscaping in Negro Communities", 1940 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Report of the NYS Flood Control Commission, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - "Rural America Lights Up"-Harry Slattery, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - NYS Annual Report of the Power of Authority, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Farm Management in Oneida County, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Organization Report, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous-Bulletins, 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Organization Reports, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Outlook Charts, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Organization Reports, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Secretary of Agriculture, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Study of the Values of Living and Working in the Rural Environment, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Organization Reports, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Teacher's College Bulletin Announcement, 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - NYS Ext. Service-Young Adult Program, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - County Agricultural Agents Reports, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-County Agr. Agents and Assistants, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Audits, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Program Planning Methods, no date (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Dipteptra of St. Vincent Williston, no date (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Series XL. Farm Management Office
  - C.B. Smith, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Draft Exceptions-Furloughs etc., 1918 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - W.A. Lloyd, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Entomology, 1918-1919 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Federal Appointments (County Agents), 1918-1919 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Singleton F.E. (Expense Accts, Checks, Etc.), 1918-1919 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Markets Division, 1918-1919 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Pay Rolls-Salary Checks, 1918-1919 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1918-1919 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Jan.-June, C.B. Smith I, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Jan.-June, C.B. Smith II, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Series XLI. Photographs
  - (Box 50)
  - People
    - C.W. Warkerton
    - Charles Palm
    - Tom Murray (Farm News Editor)
    - L.A. Chopin
    - Kenneth Cole
    - Flansburgh
    - Edward Thomson
    - C.W. Warburton
    - "Spike"
    - Unidentified Men
  - County Agricultural Agents Conferences
    - 1917
    - 1920
    - 1927
    - 1937
    - 1944
    - 1946
    - 1947
  - Dairy School, 1905
  - Otto Hillig and Holger Hoiriis with the monoplane "Liberty", 1931
  - Extension Workers Creed